ERIC THORFINNSON

Web Developer / Musician

PROJECTS

Not Your Thoughts - www.notyourthoughts.com

Deployed February 2020

- Full-stack mindfulness-based gamified journalling web app
- Independently developed with MongoDB, Node/Express, and React

Feel - Thai Massage & Yoga

Deployed June 2020

 Independently developed for a yoga studio in Stjärnsund, Sweden with PostgreSQL, Node/Express, and React

BigDeal

Deployed July 2020

- Price-tracking app utilizing the MERN stack with SocketIO, AWS,
 Puppeteer & Material-Ui
- Responsible for implementing Auth with JWT & Cookies, AWS photo upload / storage, Web Scraping of Amazon, Ebay & Craigslist with Puppeteer, and fleshing out Socket
- Built for Hatchways Co-op Development program

EXPERIENCE

Music Teacher | Elite Music Academy

JUN 2017 - 2019, TORONTO, ON

 Taught Guitar, Drums, Piano, Ukulele and Music Theory to hundreds of students from ages 4-65

AV Technician | Park Boulevard Productions

JAN 2013 - 2015, NYC, NY

- Mixed and helped set up sound for a wide variety of corporate events across NYC
- Worked at the New York Public Library with clients such as Mike Tyson and Neil Gaiman

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, Web Development

SEP 2019 - DEC 2019, TORONTO, ON

Berklee College Of Music | Bachelors in Music Production & Engineering

MAY 2008 - 2012, BOSTON, MA | Dean's List 2008-2010

ethorf@gmail.com 289-838-2835 www.ethorf.com linkedin.com/ericthorfinnson github.com/ethorf

Languages

HTML, CSS, Javascript

Technologies / Frameworks

React, SASS, MongoDB, Postgres, Puppeteer, Socket.IO, AWS, Material-UI, Redux

PROFILE

My goal is to empower people to create mindful and sustainable relationships through their use of technology.

INTERESTS

I am deeply fascinated by how understanding the human mind can help us actively work to better ourselves, our planet, and our relationships. I have a voracious appetite for books, art and travel, and have been a serious meditator for over a decade.